#### ADENIGBA AHMED ADEFOLARIN

No 4 olarenwaju Oloruntele street, opposite mobil, mile 12, Lagos State +2349011464174
Lameda789@gmail.com

A junior developer with a strong command of HTML and CSS, at least one year of experience, and some knowledge of JavaScript. I've worked on a variety of projects, both solo and collaborative, where my exceptional HTML and CSS skills have been put to use. I'm also familiar with how to utilize GitHub and Git because I've used both programs when working on both solo and group projects.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Date of Birth: 12/12/1997 State of Origin: KWARA

L.G.A: IFELODUN Nationality: NIGERIA Marital Status: SINGLE

### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Usmanu Danfodiyo University
Bachelor's Degree (MICROBIOLOGY)

**Sokoto, Sokoto State** November 2014 - September 2018

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

TIIDELAB Abuja

**Prefellowship Cohort** 

March 2022 – April 2022

Using only HTML and CSS, I was able to construct and launch both my personal web portfolio and a contact page for an e-commerce website within the duration of the program. During the program, I was also able to hone my skills in using Git and GitHub because my team and I were given a group project where the requirement for cooperation necessitated the usage of these tools.

TIIDELAB

Cohort 4 Fellowship

UNE 2022 – presentl

Cohort 4 Fellowship JUNE 2022 – presently

React and JavaScript are two new frameworks I'm learning while working as an intern at TIIDELAB. I'm also brushing up on my soft skills, which will help me evolve into a developer who stands out both technically and intellectually.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

•	Familiar	with	python	programming	language.
---	----------	------	--------	-------------	-----------

- Expert in Frontend Software Development (HTML and CSS)
- Familiar with the use of Git and GitHub

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Critical and Analytical thinking
- Attention to details
- Leadership skills
- Team work
- Digital skills
- Creative
- · Good communication skills

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND CERTIFICATION

• Certificate of completion (TIIDELab Cohort 4 Prefellowship Program (Fundamentals of Software Development))

# REFERENCE

Available upon request.